A Guide to the L. T. Christian Funeral Home Records, 1912-1986
Library of Virginia
- Reid, Rosa Lee, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 58)
- Reinhart, Mary Lutomski, 1978 (Box 37, Folder 9)
- Reintz, Annie Rebecca Bowling, 1939 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Reisler, Joseph Thomas, 1966 (Box 26, Folder 16)
- Reith, J. Reginald, 1959 (Box 19, Folder 21)
- Reith, Minnie B., 1967 (Box 27, Folder 18)
- Rennie, James Gordon, 1975 (Box 34, Folder 9)
- Rennie, Margaret H., 1978 (Box 37, Folder 9)
- Rennie, Nettie Belle, 1960 (Box 20, Folder 24)
- Rennolds, Edmund Addison, 1953 (Box 13, Folder 17)
- Rennolds, Nellie Addison, 1950 (Box 10, Folder 25)
- Rennolds, Robert Gordon, 1960 (Box 20, Folder 24)
- Rexrode, Sullie Eugene, 1961 (Box 21, Folder 20)
- Reynolds, Charles Price, 1973 (Box 34, Folder 9)
- Reynolds, David Parham, 1966 (Box 26, Folder 16)
- Reynolds, Elizabeth Crown, 1953 (Box 13, Folder 17)
- Reynolds, Harriet, 1975 (Box 34, Folder 9)
- Reynolds, Hila M., 1943 (Box 4, Folder 16)
- Reynolds, Jane Parker, 1971 (Box 31, Folder 18)
- Reynolds, Lillie Riggin, 1933 (Box 1, Folder 28)
- Reynolds, Marian H., 1977 (Box 36, Folder 12)
- Reynolds, Richard Roland, 1966 (Box 26, Folder 16)
- Reynolds, Richard S. (2 folders), 1955 (Box 15, Folder 21)
- Reynolds, Virginia Dickinson (also see oversize item), 1966 (Box 26, Folder 16)
- Rhamstine, Lisette L., 1985 (Box 41, Folder 6)
- Rhea, John M., 1962 (Box 22, Folder 21)
- Rheutan, Allen Carroll, 1951 (Box 11, Folder 22)
- Rheutan, Donald E., 1981 (Box 39, Folder 5)
- Rheutan, Gertrude Everett, 1941 (Box 4, Folder 16)
- Rheutan, Isaac L., 1945 (Box 6, Folder 10)
- Rheutan, Jennie Barksdale, 1982 (Box 39, Folder 5)
- Rheutan, Richard D., 1977 (Box 36, Folder 12)
- Rhoads, Katherine, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 58)
- Rhoads, Webster S., 1941 (Box 4, Folder 16)
- Rhoads, Webster S., Jr., 1967 (Box 27, Folder 18)
- Rhodenizer, Earl, 1961 (Box 21, Folder 20)
- Rhodes, Mildred Brooks, 1981 (Box 39, Folder 6)
- Riaz, Abdul, 1984 (Box 41, Folder 6)
- Ribble, Constance M., 1972 (Box 32, Folder 18)
- Ribble, George Wallace, 1954 (Box 14, Folder 22)
- Ribble, W. Leigh, 1979 (Box 37, Folder 9)
- Rice, Belle Martin, 1985 (Box 41, Folder 7)
- Rice, Borden Prather, 1968 (Box 28, Folder 18)
- Rice, Carry Vick, 1973 (Box 34, Folder 10)
- Rice, Drury L., 1947 (Box 7, Folder 19)
- Rice, Edwin Catesby, 1936 (Box 1, Folder 44)
- Rice, Hattie Christie Wilton, 1964 (Box 24, Folder 18)
- Rice, Lucy Clark, 1955 (Box 15, Folder 21)
- Rice, Minnie Vaughan, 1952 (Box 12, Folder 22)
- Rice, Nellie G., 1956 (Box 16, Folder 18)
- Rice, R. Coleman, 1967 (Box 27, Folder 18)
- Rice, Richard N., 1946 (Box 6, Folder 10)
- Rice, William Augustus, 1954 (Box 14, Folder 22)
- Rich, Obb Moseley, 1949 (Box 9, Folder 25)
- Rich, Rosa Pearl, 1948 (Box 8, Folder 25)
- Richarde, John Charles, 1947 (Box 7, Folder 19)
- Richards, Charles Hamilton, 1973 (Box 34, Folder 10)
- Richards, Constance Sutton, 1970 (Box 30, Folder 20)
- Richards, Evelyn C., 1959 (Box 19, Folder 21)
- Richards, Gertrude Randolph Bramlett, 1963 (Box 23, Folder 20)
- Richards, Margaret Topham, 1930 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Richardson, [infant], 1931 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Richardson, Ann Myers, 1968 (Box 28, Folder 18)
- Richardson, Anne Elizabeth, 1931 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Richardson, Anne Pritchett, 1943 (Box 4, Folder 17)
- Richardson, Catherine Cary, 1942 (disinterred) (Box 4, Folder 17)
- Richardson, Charles B., 1942 (Box 4, Folder 17)
- Richardson, Elizabeth Wellford, 1958 (Box 18, Folder 21)
- Richardson, Florence Buford, 1953 (Box 13, Folder 17)
- Richardson, Jessie Herbert, 1953 (Box 13, Folder 17)
- Richardson, Julia Frances, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 58)
- Richardson, Julia Wickham, 1941 (Box 4, Folder 17)
- Richardson, Laura Lee, 1955 (Box 15, Folder 21)
- Richardson, Laura Morse, 1965 (Box 25, Folder 23)
- Richardson, Lucia Peyton, 1942 (disinterred) (Box 4, Folder 17)
- Richardson, Marion Hunter, 1939 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Richardson, Mattie L., 1930 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Richardson, Octavia Christian, 1956 (Box 16, Folder 18)
- Richardson, Page Grymes, 1972 (Box 32, Folder 18)
- Richardson, Richard Cunningham, 1961 (Box 21, Folder 20)
- Richardson, Richard Emmett, 1942 (disinterred) (Box 4, Folder 17)
- Richardson, Robert Emmett, 1929 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Richardson, Sadie Atlee, 1963 (Box 23, Folder 21)
- Richardson, Thomas Randolph, 1933 (Box 1, Folder 28)
- Richardson, Thomas Randolph, 1942 (disinterred) (Box 4, Folder 17)
- Richardson, Wilbur Percy, 1952 (Box 12, Folder 22)
- Richardson, Willard Hersey, 1933 (Box 1, Folder 28)
- Richardson, William Edward, 1931 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Richardson, William Fletcher, Jr., 1941 (Box 4, Folder 17)
- Richardson, William Fred, 1943 (Box 4, Folder 17)
- Richeson, Charlett T., 1969 (Box 29, Folder 14)
- Richeson, Henry Taylor, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 58)
- Richeson, McGrady, 1949 (Box 9, Folder 25)
- Rickert, Edna East, 1956 (Box 16, Folder 18)
- Ricketts, Emmie Blanche, 1966 (Box 26, Folder 16)
- Ricketts, George Albert, 1970 (Box 30, Folder 20)
- Ricketts, Mary Blanche McGhee, 1945 (Box 6, Folder 10)
- Ricks, Anne Ryland, 1953 (Box 13, Folder 17)
- Ricks, James Hoge, 1958 (Box 18, Folder 21)
- Ricks, Katharine Crenshaw, 1969 (Box 29, Folder 14)
- Ricks, Mary Virginia, 1984 (Box 41, Folder 7)
- Ricks, Richard Arnold, 1956 (Box 16, Folder 18)
- Riddick, Clarence T., 1941 (Box 4, Folder 17)
- Riddick, Francis L., 1950 (Box 10, Folder 25)
- Riddick, George A., 1940 (Box 2, Folder 16)
- Riddick, Helen Smith, 1954 (Box 14, Folder 22)
- Riddick, Henry D., 1936 (Box 1, Folder 44)
- Riddick, Junius R., 1945 (Box 6, Folder 10)
- Riddick, Loulie McDowell, 1945 (Box 6, Folder 10)
- Riddick, Mary T., 1928 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Riddle, Fannie Chandler, 1960 (Box 20, Folder 24)
- Riddle, Morton, 1941 (Box 4, Folder 17)
- Ridgaway, Cara A., 1941 (Box 4, Folder 17)
- Ridgeway, Frances Bristow, 1982 (Box 39, Folder 6)
- Ridout, Emily Bliss, 1960 (Box 20, Folder 24)
- Ridout, John, n. d. (Box 2, Folder 19)
- Riely, Anne, 1951 (Box 11, Folder 22)
- Riely, Henry Carrington, 1947 (Box 7, Folder 19)
- Riely, James E., 1975 (Box 34, Folder 10)
- Riely, Nettie Evans, 1951 (Box 11, Folder 22)
- Rienhart, Joseph B., 1939 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Riethmiller, Murvin W., 1968 (Box 28, Folder 18)
- Riethmiller, Phillip Christian, 1939 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Riggleman, Huldah, 1936 (Box 1, Folder 44)
- Riggs, James H., 1948 (Box 8, Folder 25)
- Rike, Laura Ramsey, 1969 (Box 29, Folder 14)
- Riley, Ethel Woolf, 1978 (Box 37, Folder 9)
- Riley, Ruth W., 1945 (Box 6, Folder 10)
- Rinehart, Priscilla Phillips, 1973 (Box 34, Folder 10)
- Rinker, Robert Bruce, 1936 (Box 1, Folder 44)
- Rinkes, Saraphene L., 1927 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Ripley, Arthur P., 1937 (Box 1, Folder 50)
- Ripley, Edna Forbes, 1960 (Box 20, Folder 24)
- Risenhoover, Ricky Eugene [infant], 1962 (Box 22, Folder 21)
- Rives, Clarence Tompkins, 1973 (Box 34, Folder 10)
- Roach, Walter P., 1932 (Box 1, Folder 23)
- Roache, Edith Merrill, 1937 (Box 1, Folder 50)
- Roane, E. Pittman, 1965 (Box 25, Folder 23)
- Robb, John Bernard, 1965 (Box 25, Folder 23)
- Roberts, Alma Owens, 1945 (Box 6, Folder 11)
- Roberts, Anna, 1955 (Box 15, Folder 22)
- Roberts, Annie Taylor Elam, 1962 (Box 22, Folder 21)
- Roberts, Bessie Spotts, 1956 (Box 16, Folder 18)
- Roberts, Constance S., 1938 (Box 1, Folder 58)
- Roberts, Edith Mae, 1937 (Box 1, Folder 50)
- Roberts, Edward A., 1946 (Box 6, Folder 11)
- Roberts, Ethel Van Hook, 1930 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Roberts, George J., 1948 (Box 8, Folder 26)
- Roberts, Henry Clarke, 1956 (Box 16, Folder 19)
- Roberts, James Elam, 1964 (Box 24, Folder 18)
- Roberts, Judith Kemp, 1949 (Box 9, Folder 25)
- Roberts, Leslie Lee, 1948 (Box 8, Folder 26)
- Roberts, Lucien Wood, 1946 (Box 6, Folder 11)
- Roberts, Lucy Mason, 1957 (Box 17, Folder 18)
- Roberts, Mary Sue, 1932 (Box 1, Folder 23)
- Roberts, Mildred Talley, 1955 (Box 15, Folder 22)
- Roberts, Nellie Gresham, 1959 (Box 19, Folder 21)
- Roberts, Paul Steven, 1968 (Box 28, Folder 18)
- Roberts, Richard Whitfield, 1957 (Box 17, Folder 18)
- Roberts, Robert R., 1962 (Box 22, Folder 21)
- Roberts, Robert Richford, Jr., 1935 (Box 1, Folder 37)
- Roberts, Rufus G., Jr., 1984 (Box 41, Folder 7)
- Roberts, Saxe Coburg, 1937 (Box 1, Folder 50)
- Roberts, William N., 1943 (Box 4, Folder 17)
- Robertson, C. J., 1925 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Robertson, Charles B., 1958 (Box 18, Folder 21)
- Robertson, Elizabeth Lewis Irvine, 1944 (Box 6, Folder 11)
- Robertson, Frances V., 1950 (Box 10, Folder 25)
- Robertson, Inez Bruce, 1963 (Box 23, Folder 21)
- Robertson, James William, 1954 (Box 14, Folder 22)
- Robertson, John Ashby, 1961 (Box 21, Folder 20)
- Robertson, Mary G., 1938 (Box 1, Folder 58)
- Robertson, Mary Vawter, 1944 (Box 6, Folder 11)
- Robertson, Maude Rowlett, 1969 (Box 29, Folder 14)
- Robertson, Rebecca J., 1929 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Robertson, Walter, 1970 (Box 30, Folder 21)
- Robey, Luella Taylor, 1951 (Box 11, Folder 23)
- Robey, Mildred Lee Bryant, 1983 (Box 39, Folder 6)
- Robins, Arebella Davis, 1931 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Robins, Charles Russell, 1948 (Box 8, Folder 26)
- Robins, Emma Francis Rose, 1972 (Box 32, Folder 18)
- Robins, Franklin Davis, 1966 (Box 26, Folder 17)
- Robins, Hubel, 1965 (Box 25, Folder 24)
- Robins, Susan Clay, 1950 (Box 10, Folder 25)
- Robins, Virginia Park, 1959 (Box 19, Folder 21)
- Robinson, Agnes C., 1938 (Box 1, Folder 58)
- Robinson, Alfred Francis, 1985 (Box 41, Folder 7)
- Robinson, Annie F., 1962 (Box 22, Folder 21)
- Robinson, Charles M., 1932 (Box 1, Folder 23)
- Robinson, Constance Harris, 1957 (Box 17, Folder 18)
- Robinson, Cornelia Walker, 1936 (Box 1, Folder 44)
- Robinson, E. Shirley, 1962 (Box 22, Folder 22)
- Robinson, Edward Trent, 1940 (Box 2, Folder 16)
- Robinson, Ellyson Shirley, 1955 (Box 15, Folder 22)
- Robinson, Eugene, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 58)
- Robinson, George Wilson, 1964 (Box 24, Folder 18)
- Robinson, Gurney W., 1939 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Robinson, Hester, 1933 (Box 1, Folder 28)
- Robinson, Inez Montague, 1956 (Box 16, Folder 19)
- Robinson, James D., 1935 (Box 1, Folder 37)
- Robinson, James Taylor, 1963 (Box 23, Folder 21)
- Robinson, John B., 1978 (Box 37, Folder 9)
- Robinson, John Enders, 1943 (Box 4, Folder 17)
- Robinson, John Vernon, 1945 (Box 6, Folder 11)
- Robinson, Katharine Spotswood, 1959 (Box 19, Folder 21)
- Robinson, Lee Lemar, 1962 (Box 22, Folder 22)
- Robinson, Lenora B., 1935 (Box 1, Folder 37)
- Robinson, Littleton Tazwell, 1934 (Box 1, Folder 32)
- Robinson, Louise Wilson, 1966 (Box 26, Folder 17)
- Robinson, Lula Thomas, 1955 (Box 15, Folder 22)
- Robinson, Margaret Crockett, 1964 (Box 24, Folder 18)
- Robinson, Martha W., 1956 (Box 16, Folder 19)
- Robinson, Mary England, 1928 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Robinson, Morgan P., 1943 (Box 4, Folder 17)
- Robinson, Robert Randolph, 1942 (Box 4, Folder 17)
- Robinson, Ruby Work, 1963 (Box 23, Folder 21)
- Robinson, William Lee [infant], 1949 (Box 9, Folder 25)
- Roche, Frederick Gibbs, 1951 (Box 11, Folder 23)
- Rockey, Marcia D., 1929 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Roden, Margret Hewett, 1937 (Box 1, Folder 50)
- Rodenbaugh, J. F., 1937 (Box 1, Folder 50)
- Rodgers, Katherine, 1957 (Box 17, Folder 19)
- Rodwell, Alice Ford, 1944 (Box 6, Folder 11)
- Rody, George Allen, 1944 (Box 6, Folder 11)
- Rogers, Beulah Cleo Dickerson, 1966 (Box 26, Folder 17)
- Rogers, George Wesley, 1967 (Box 27, Folder 18)
- Rogers, James Lewis, 1929 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Rogers, Roy V., 1946 (Box 6, Folder 11)
- Rogers, Sallie Knight, 1962 (Box 22, Folder 22)
- Rogers, William J., 1953 (Box 13, Folder 18)
- Rohland, Louise Williams, 1974 (Box 34, Folder 11)
- Roland, Virgil Davis, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 58)
- Roles, William Russell, 1935 (Box 1, Folder 37)
- Rollings, Millie H., 1949 (Box 9, Folder 25)
- Rollins, James, 1956 (Box 16, Folder 19)
- Rollins, Jane Lee, 1959 (Box 19, Folder 22)
- Romero, Rosalina Liquet Rodriquez, 1981 (Box 39, Folder 6)
- Rooney, Robert Newton, 1937 (Box 1, Folder 50)
- Roper, Lonsdale, Joseph, 1951 (Box 11, Folder 23)
- Rorbough, Virgil, 1961 (Box 21, Folder 20)
- Rose, Charlotte Perry, 1937 (Box 1, Folder 50)
- Rose, Forrest, 1937 (Box 1, Folder 50)
- Rose, Gladys Beale, 1965 (Box 25, Folder 24)
- Rose, Helen Tanner, 1961 (Box 21, Folder 20)
- Rose, Hugh Fontaine, 1968 (Box 28, Folder 18)
- Rose, James Garland, 1951 (Box 11, Folder 23)
- Rose, James Garland, 1973 (Box 34, Folder 11)
- Rose, Lillian G., 1925 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Rose, Mabel Ladd, 1939 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Rose, Marion S., 1959 (Box 19, Folder 22)
- Rosebro, Ben Morrison, 1936 (Box 1, Folder 44)
- Rosebro, Mary Watkins, 1955 (Box 15, Folder 22)
- Rosenblatt, Joel Harry, 1963 (Box 23, Folder 21)
- Ross, William Eldridge, 1966 (Box 26, Folder 17)
- Rosson, Annie Calvert, 1947 (Box 7, Folder 19)
- Roundtree, Russell S., Jr., 1947 (Box 7, Folder 19)
- Rouse, Jasper Marcus, 1949 (Box 9, Folder 25)
- Routt, Mary Pulliam, 1929 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Rowe, Edwin Park, 1960 (Box 20, Folder 24)
- Rowe, Elizabeth Bennett, 1951 (Box 11, Folder 23)
- Rowe, James Francis, 1941 (Box 4, Folder 18)
- Rowe, Jane Prescott, 1942 (Box 4, Folder 18)
- Rowe, Samuel Clopton, 1953 (Box 13, Folder 18)
- Rowland, Joseph Stuart, 1963 (Box 23, Folder 21)
- Rowland, Lucy Estelle, 1946 (Box 6, Folder 11)
- Rowlett, Edith Cottingham, 1965 (Box 25, Folder 24)
- Rowlett, Eleanor Patterson, 1949 (Box 9, Folder 25)
- Rowlett, Florence Elizabeth, 1948 (Box 8, Folder 26)
- Rowlett, Georgianna S., 1925 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Rowlett, James Ernest, 1959 (Box 19, Folder 22)
- Royall, Anne Keith, 1965 (Box 25, Folder 24)
- Royall, Hilary Herbert, 1952 (Box 12, Folder 23)
- Royall, Lois Watson, 1961 (Box 21, Folder 20)
- Royall, Page Aylett, 1942 (Box 4, Folder 18)
- Royall, William L, Jr., 1941 (Box 4, Folder 18)
- Royall, William L. (disinterment), 1944 (Box 6, Folder 12)
- Royer, Ethel Drake, 1984 (Box 41, Folder 7)
- Royer, Ethel Hough, 1966 (Box 26, Folder 17)
- Royer, John B., 1963 (Box 23, Folder 21)
- Royster, Corrie Poe, 1931 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Royster, Mary W., 1935 (Box 1, Folder 37)
- Royster, Oce H., 1943 (Box 4, Folder 18)
- Royster, William Savage, 1931 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Rubis, Paul, 1950 (Box 10, Folder 25)
- Rucker, Dana H., 1949 (Box 9, Folder 25)
- Rucker, Geneva, 1957 (Box 17, Folder 19)
- Rucker, Josephine McRae, 1981 (Box 39, Folder 6)
- Rucker, Lucy Harrison, 1956 (Box 16, Folder 19)
- Rucker, Lydia Atwood, 1946 (Box 6, Folder 12)
- Rucker, Marvin Pierce, 1953 (Box 13, Folder 18)
- Rucker, Mary P., 1975 (Box 34, Folder 11)
- Rudd, Emma Beatrice, 1977 (Box 36, Folder 12)
- Rudd, Lawson Genevieve, 1936 (Box 1, Folder 44)
- Rudd, Mabelle Welsh, 1962 (Box 22, Folder 22)
- Rudd, Zara Dugsdale, 1949 (Box 9, Folder 25)
- Ruffin, Alice Lorraine, 1931 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Ruffin, Anne Harrison, 1985 (Box 41, Folder 8)
- Ruffin, Benjamin Allen, 1939 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Ruffin, Charles Lorraine, 1951 (Box 11, Folder 23)
- Ruffin, Edmond Lorraine, 1947 (Box 7, Folder 19)
- Ruffin, Edmund Lorraine, 1943 (Box 4, Folder 18)
- Ruffin, Emmett Daniel [infant], 1962 (Box 22, Folder 22)
- Ruffin, Grace Helen Spear, 1950 (Box 10, Folder 25)
- Ruffin, Lelia Beverly, 1981 (Box 39, Folder 6)
- Ruffin, Mary Levering, 1954 (Box 14, Folder 23)
- Ruffin, Tallulah, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 58)
- Ruffin, Thomas Talbot, 1947 (Box 7, Folder 19)
- Ruffin, William Wilcox, 1932 (Box 1, Folder 23)
- Rufty, Hilton, 1974 (Box 34, Folder 11)
- Rufty, Hilton Bradshaw, 1933 (Box 1, Folder 28)
- Ruhl, Bessie Muhlman, 1953 (Box 13, Folder 18)
- Runkle, John Curtin, 1961 (Box 21, Folder 20)
- Ruskell, Freerick Noble, 1954 (Box 14, Folder 23)
- Ruskell, Leon Carter, 1945 (Box 6, Folder 12)
- Russell, Ines Astrid, 1976 (Box 35, Folder 14)
- Russell, Inez K., 1981 (Box 39, Folder 7)
- Russell, Joanne, 1937 (Box 1, Folder 50)
- Russell, Joanne, 1937 (interment of cremains, 1968) (Box 28, Folder 18)
- Russell, William, 1951 (Box 11, Folder 24)
- Rust, Albert Sidney, 1973 (Box 34, Folder 11)
- Rust, Inez K., 1968 (Box 28, Folder 19)
- Rust, Marshall W. (2 folders), 1942 (Box 4, Folder 18)
- Rust, Nannie King, 1956 (Box 16, Folder 19)
- Rutherford, Edith Ellett, 1957 (Box 17, Folder 19)
- Rutherford, James Thomas, 1933 (Box 1, Folder 28)
- Rutherford, Laura W., 1932 (Box 1, Folder 23)
- Rutherford, Thomas M., 1973 (Box 34, Folder 11)
- Ryan, Delia Powell, 1968 (Box 28, Folder 19)
- Ryland, Anne Claiborne Rucker, 1959 (Box 19, Folder 22)
- Ryland, Archie Garnett, 1953 (Box 13, Folder 18)
- Ryland, Elizabeth Neal, 1971 (Box 31, Folder 18)
- Ryland, Helen Haydock, 1960 (Box 20, Folder 24)
- Ryland, James F., 1951 (Box 11, Folder 24)
- Ryland, John Muscoe Garnett, 1952 (Box 12, Folder 23)
- Ryland, John Newton, Jr., 1938 (Box 1, Folder 58)
- Ryland, Mary Boyd, 1983 (Box 39, Folder 7)
- Ryland, Mary Virginia, 1970 (Box 30, Folder 21)
- Ryland, Samuel Peachy, 1954 (Box 14, Folder 23)
- Ryland, Samuel Peachy, Jr., 1960 (Box 20, Folder 24)
- Ryland, W. Bradford, 1978 (Box 37, Folder 9)
- Ryland, William S., 1983 (Box 39, Folder 7)
- Sacrey, Lottie Parrish Gough, 1964 (Box 24, Folder 19)
- Sadler, Joseph (see Blackburn-Dicken family), (disinterred 1969) (Box 29, Folder 3)
- Sadler, Lulie Evans, 1943 (Box 4, Folder 19)
- Sadler, Victoria Blackburn (see Blackburn-Dicken family), (disinterred 1969) (Box 29, Folder 3)
- Sadler, William Frances, 1969 (Box 29, Folder 14)
- Sainsbury, Esther Harriet, 1952 (Box 12, Folder 23)
- Sainsbury, Richard C., 1936 (Box 1, Folder 45)
- Sale, Ada Todd, 1937 (Box 1, Folder 51)
- Sale, Annie Belle S., 1964 (Box 24, Folder 19)
- Sale, Charlotte Louisa, 1936 (Box 1, Folder 45)
- Sale, Emmett Collins, 1958 (Box 18, Folder 22)
- Sale, Ethel Melton, 1935 (Box 1, Folder 38)
- Sale, James Winston, 1956 (Box 16, Folder 19)
- Sale, Millie Ann, 1929 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Sale, Sue Evans, 1941 (Box 4, Folder 19)
- Sale, William Goodridge, 1943 (Box 4, Folder 19)
- Sale, William Wilson, 1939 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Salley, George Elmore, 1960 (Box 20, Folder 25)
- Salley, Ryan Bruce, 1970 (Box 30, Folder 21)
- Salley, T. Rayson, 1948 (Box 8, Folder 27)
- Salling, Margaret, 1937 (Box 1, Folder 51)
- Salmon, Margaret, 1954 (Box 14, Folder 23)
- Salrin, Dorothy Blow, 1974 (Box 34, Folder 12)
- Sample, John Jacob, 1954 (Box 14, Folder 23)
- Sampson, Emma Speede, 1947 (Box 7, Folder 20)
- Sams, Walter Lee, 1965 (Box 25, Folder 24)
- Sanders, Emma Lorraine, 1971 (Box 31, Folder 18)
- Sanders, Katy Thomas Buford, 1963 (Box 23, Folder 22)
- Sanders, Louise C., 1984 (Box 41, Folder 8)
- Sanders, Mamie Redd, 1975 (Box 34, Folder 12)
- Sanders, Stuart, 1941 (Box 4, Folder 19)
- Sanders, Walter T. T., 1930 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Sanders, Willis Sublet, 1946 (Box 6, Folder 12)
- Sandford, C. Marshall, 1956 (Box 16, Folder 20)
- Sandridge, Sarah Ann, 1934 (Box 1, Folder 32)
- Sands, Tucker Kinsford, 1939 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Sands, Virginia, 1964 (Box 24, Folder 19)
- Sandy, Edwin Scott, 1982 (Box 39, Folder 7)
- Sandy, Nellie Hall, 1950 (Box 10, Folder 26)
- Sanford, Ada Woodriff, 1945 (Box 6, Folder 12)
- Sanford, Helen May, 1976 (Box 35, Folder 14)
- Sangster, Pattie, 1958 (Box 18, Folder 22)
- Sarvay, Cornelia Augusta, 1940 (Box 2, Folder 17)
- Sarvay, Lydia Booth, 1983 (Box 39, Folder 7)
- Sarvay, Mary Booker, 1970 (Box 30, Folder 21)
- Sarvay, Rufus Henry, Jr., 1949 (Box 9, Folder 26)
- Sarvay, Sally Marvin, 1946 (Box 6, Folder 12)
- Sarvay, Sarah Jane, 1933 (Box 1, Folder 29)
- Sarvay, Walter D., 1959 (Box 19, Folder 22)
- Satchell, Elizabeth M., 1935 (Box 1, Folder 38)
- Saterfield, Calvin, 1936 (Box 1, Folder 45)
- Satterfield, Calvin, Jr., 1941 (Box 4, Folder 19)
- Satterfield, Susie Walker, 1939 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Satterwhite, Clarence E., 1970 (Box 30, Folder 21)
- Sauer, [infant] son of Tremaine Ernest Armstrong, 1952 (Box 12, Folder 23)
- Sauer, Conrad F., Jr., 1953 (Box 13, Folder 19)
- Sauer, Mary, 1979 (Box 37, Folder 10)
- Saums, Charlotte Beckman, 1960 (Box 20, Folder 25)
- Saunders, Alwyn Dabney, 1968 (Box 28, Folder 19)
- Saunders, Annie Moss Taylor, 1983 (Box 39, Folder 8)
- Saunders, Arthur Bruce, 1941 (Box 4, Folder 19)
- Saunders, Blanche Gertrude, 1935 (Box 1, Folder 38)
- Saunders, Carlton J., 1938 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Saunders, Christopher Walton, 1937 (Box 1, Folder 51)
- Saunders, Creagh Burroughs, 1945 (Box 6, Folder 12)
- Saunders, Fannie Seabrook, 1943 (Box 4, Folder 19)
- Saunders, George H., 1936 (Box 1, Folder 45)
- Saunders, Grace Ercelle Cottrell, 1968 (Box 28, Folder 19)
- Saunders, Ida Bolling, 1967 (Box 27, Folder 18)
- Saunders, Julia Edwards, 1966 (Box 26, Folder 17)
- Saunders, Julius Roy, 1958 (Box 18, Folder 22)
- Saunders, Junius Morris, 1943 (Box 4, Folder 19)
- Saunders, Martha Brown, 1933 (Box 1, Folder 29)
- Saunders, Mary E., 1946 (Box 6, Folder 12)
- Saunders, Nellie M., 1979 (Box 37, Folder 10)
- Saunders, Richard Anderson, 1971 (Box 31, Folder 18)
- Saunders, Rose Gray, 1975 (Box 34, Folder 12)
- Saunders, Tabitha Coleman, 1958 (Box 18, Folder 22)
- Saunders, Virginia A., 1947 (Box 7, Folder 20)
- Saunders, Wallace Coleman, 1948 (Box 8, Folder 27)
- Saunders, William Bailey, 1930 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Saunders, William Bailey, Jr., 1937 (Box 1, Folder 51)
- Saunders, William Lynn, 1933 (Box 1, Folder 29)
- Saunders, William Olynthus, 1933 (Box 1, Folder 29)
- Savage, Olivia Richardson, 1961 (Box 21, Folder 21)
- Saville, Allen Jeter, 1947 (Box 7, Folder 20)
- Saville, Charles O., 1942 (Box 4, Folder 19)
- Saville, John Fitzwilson, 1942 (Box 4, Folder 19)
- Saville, Keith Woodson, 1941 (Box 4, Folder 19)
- Sawyer, Clara H., 1971 (Box 31, Folder 18)
- Scales, Mary Roberta Sale, 1957 (Box 17, Folder 19)
- Scales, Walter Yancey, 1952 (Box 12, Folder 23)
- Scannel, Walter William, 1944 (Box 6, Folder 12)
- Schaadt, Charles Williams, 1935 (Box 1, Folder 38)
- Schaefer, Anne Pender C., 1975 (Box 34, Folder 12)
- Schaefer, Charles Martin, 1965 (Box 25, Folder 24)
- Schaefer, George M., 1943 (Box 4, Folder 19)
- Schaefer, Margaret McKee, 1974 (Box 34, Folder 12)
- Schaefer, Mary Anita, 1968 (Box 28, Folder 19)
- Schaefer, Minnie Harris, 1968 (Box 28, Folder 19)
- Schaefer, Rosa Virginia, 1966 (Box 26, Folder 18)
- Schaffer, Harry Vernon, 1954 (Box 14, Folder 23)
- Schaffer, Robert Gresham, 1966 (Box 26, Folder 18)
- Schell, Gay Warren, 1948 (Box 8, Folder 27)
- Scherer, Clarence Junius, 1945 (Box 6, Folder 12)
- Scherer, Frank Gottlieb, 1968 (Box 28, Folder 19)
- Scherer, Nannie Ethel, 1960 (Box 20, Folder 25)
- Scherer, Stuart Curtis, Jr., 1946 (Box 6, Folder 12)
- Scherer, William F., 1966 (Box 26, Folder 18)
- Schilling, Florence E., 1960 (Box 20, Folder 25)
- Schlesinger, Bella Emsheimer, 1938 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Schmidt, Celestine Garcia, 1961 (Box 21, Folder 21)
- Schmidt, Edward George, 1968 (Box 28, Folder 20)
- Schmidt, Marie, 1970 (Box 30, Folder 21)
- Schmidt, Martha Lee Stevenson, 1959 (Box 19, Folder 22)
- Schmidt, Robert Charles, 1944 (Box 6, Folder 13)
- Schmidt, Rosa B., 1948 (Box 8, Folder 27)
- Schmidt, Wilhelmine Boschen, 1951 (Box 11, Folder 24)
- Schmitz, Georgia Fowler, 1975 (Box 34, Folder 12)
- Schoefield, Harriett Ella, 1932 (Box 1, Folder 24)
- Schoelles, Cyrus Philip, 1936 (Box 1, Folder 45)
- Schofield, Eliza Plummer, 1960 (Box 20, Folder 25)
- Schofield, Frances A., 1976 (Box 35, Folder 14)
- Schofield, James Wister, 1955 (Box 15, Folder 23)
- Schreck, Dalton L., 1965 (Box 25, Folder 24)
- Schremp, Anna Schleicher, 1955 (Box 15, Folder 23)
- Schremp, Charles Mathias, 1942 (Box 4, Folder 20)
- Schueler, Maria Eliza, 1955 (Box 15, Folder 23)
- Schuirmann, Williams Carter, 1952 (Box 12, Folder 23)
- Schumacher, Anne, 1976 (Box 35, Folder 14)
- Schumacher, Earnest D., 1956 (Box 16, Folder 20)
- Schuricht, Helen Fay, 1947 (Box 7, Folder 20)
- Schwartz, Malene Fitz, 1985 (Box 41, Folder 8)
- Sclater, Eleanor Tutwiler, 1934 (Box 1, Folder 32)
- Scott, Alice June, 1954 (Box 14, Folder 23)
- Scott, Anna Pleasants, 1929 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Scott, Childrey, 1962 (Box 22, Folder 23)